<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Orange County Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Beaches info -->
    <string name="beach_name_1">Crystal Cove State Park</string>
    <string name="beach_address_1">8471 Pacific Coast Highway, Laguna Beach, CA 92651</string>
    <string name="beach_description_1">Finding a piece of the beach that is so clean and pristine…
        Taking one back to the 40s is a delight. It is right in the middle of
        California Pacific Highway crowds and yet it is a step back in time. The restaurant had
        great food and an ambiance that matched that long ago quiet while listening to the waves
        and watching the sea birds.</string>
    <string name="beach_website_1">www.crystalcovestatepark.com</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_1">949–494–3539</string>

    <string name="beach_name_2">Newport Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_address_2">Newport Beach, CA 92660–3267</string>
    <string name="beach_description_2">There are only a few towns in the Gold Coast that reach
        the level of Newport Beach. The beaches are the best. The restaurants are unbelievable
        in style and taste. Some of the best shopping in California. Gelson\'s Market is the
        best market in Orange County. You will not see more exotic cars anywhere. You have to go
        through the harbor for a cruise and see the biggest display of private yachts and water
        front homes in California. If you are here during Christmas a restaurant view of the parade
        of lights is a must. This town is the Gem of the Gold Coast.</string>
    <string name="beach_website_2">www.newportbeachca.gov</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_2">949–644–3309</string>

    <string name="beach_name_3">Victoria Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_address_3">Victoria Drive, Laguna Beach, CA 92652</string>
    <string name="beach_description_3">The only beach that isn\'t crowded in the City of
        Laguna Beach. The local people will direct you to Aliso Beach further south if you have
        trouble finding it. They don\'t want to give up their best kept secret.
        Parking is almost non-existent, but available on PCH and across PCH off Nye\'s Pl.
        There is even an underpass below PCH to get back to the south side of PCH.
        Look for thick metal walkway rails leading down to the beach between houses.
        It looks private, but it\'s a state beach, all are welcome! Best tip,
        get there very early and enjoy the day!</string>
    <string name="beach_website_3">www.lagunabeachcity.net/cityhall/marine/beaches/victoria_beach.htm</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_3">Phone is not available😞</string>

    <string name="beach_name_4">Baby Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_address_4">24300 Dana Point Harbor Drive, Dana Point, CA 92629–2914</string>
    <string name="beach_description_4">This beach is perfect for young kids and toddlers.
        It\'s a protected section of the marina (no need to worry about high waves or undertow)
        with a roped off area for a max depth less than about 18-24\" in high tide.
        Car parking is right beside the beach so not too far to lug beach items.
        Restrooms adjacent to the beach and quite well maintained. There are Rentals right
        at the beach for SUP boards, kayaks and more!</string>
    <string name="beach_website_4">www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g32279-d6373215-Reviews-Baby_Beach-Dana_Point_California.html</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_4">Phone is not available😞</string>

    <string name="beach_name_5">Bolsa Chica State Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_address_5">18331 E Pacific Coast Hwy, Huntington Beach, CA 92648</string>
    <string name="beach_description_5">Bolsa Chica state beach has fun for all. Great beaches
        with good facilities. Lifeguards on duty for your safety. Nice place to sit and stare
        out at the beautiful ocean! Family friendly.</string>
    <string name="beach_website_5">www.parks.ca.gov/?page_id=642</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_5">714–846–3460</string>

    <string name="beach_name_6">Huntington Dog Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_address_6">E Pacific Coast Hwy and Goldenwest St, Huntington Beach, CA 92648</string>
    <string name="beach_description_6">This is a great beach to take your dog. While your dog
        runs around playing with friends you can enjoy a walk on a very beautiful beach.
        There are free bags you can use to pick up after your dog. Easy access to the beach from
        the very convenient partaking lot on Pacific Coast Highway.</string>
    <string name="beach_website_6">www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g32513-d578943-Reviews-or10-Huntington_Dog_Beach-Huntington_Beach_California.html</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_6">Phone is not available😞</string>

    <string name="beach_name_7">Salt Creek Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_address_7">Pacific Coast Hwy, Dana Point, CA 92629</string>
    <string name="beach_description_7">Easy parking, convenient walk down the hill and there is
        a beach shuttle for a buck if you do not feel like walking back up the hill with friendly
        drivers who bring you to your car. There is a wonderful walkway and the beach is just
        fabulous, a must visit!</string>
    <string name="beach_website_7">www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g32279-d4112527-Reviews-Salt_Creek_Beach-Dana_Point_California.html</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_7">Phone is not available😞</string>

    <string name="beach_name_8">1,000 Steps Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_address_8">31972 Pacific Coast Hwy, Laguna Beach, CA 92651</string>
    <string name="beach_description_8">A fun and great workout if you\'re challenging
        yourself for a climb up these stairs. Beautiful Laguna with its beach breeze and sun
        will give you the motivation to complete the task. It\'s not 1000, but it will seem
        like it once you\'ve gone up those stairs a few times. Many have come to challenge
        themselves by going up these steps over 5 or 10 times. Give it a try and enjoy the
        beach and waves and sunset afterwards.</string>
    <string name="beach_website_8">www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g32588-d561800-Reviews-1_000_Steps_Beach-Laguna_Beach_California.html</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_8">Phone is not available😞</string>

    <string name="beach_name_9">Seal Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_address_9">Seal Beach, CA 90740</string>
    <string name="beach_description_9">SB is smaller than some of the surrounding beach towns.
        But it\'s well worth a visit. The beach is nice and is perfect to watch the sun set.
        There\'s a shopping area and plenty of restaurants. Paid parking is available or if
        you\'re lucky, you may find free parking. Have fun!</string>
    <string name="beach_website_9">www.sealbeachca.gov</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_9">562–431–2527</string>

    <string name="beach_name_10">Corona Del Mar State Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_address_10">Corona del Mar State Beach, 3001 Ocean Blvd, Corona Del Mar, CA 92625</string>
    <string name="beach_description_10">The beach itself is beautiful and there are ample
        reviews already. But, look up to the cliff side and hike up. It is a beautiful view
        from the cliff above either overseeing the beach or the architecture of the homes. Plenty
        of street parking if one prefer to drive up but do show respects for the local residents
        for they are the ones who provide us with this scenic street.</string>
    <string name="beach_website_10">www.parks.ca.gov/?page_id=652</string>
    <string name="beach_phone_10">949–644–3151</string>

    <!-- Food places info -->
    <string name="food_place_name_1">Portos Bakery &amp; Cafe</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_1">7640 Beach Blvd, Buena Park, CA 90620</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_1">More than a year on, the Buena Park location of
        Porto\'s Bakery &amp; Cafe continues to thrive. This massive outlet for Cuban
        baked goods and savory-side stuff is as slammed as it gets most days, with folks lining
        up for potato balls and whatever else they can get their hands on.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_1">www.portosbakery.com</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_1">714–670–6427</string>

    <string name="food_place_name_2">Pour Vida</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_2">185 W. Center Street Promenade, Anaheim, CA, 92805</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_2">Jimmy Martinez continues the Anaheim dining revolution
        with Pour Vida Latin Flavor, his casual corner spot with small outdoor seating and big
        flavors. It\'s a hit with the walking crowd that passes by out front, and has helped to
        establish Martinez as one of Orange County\'s most recognizable chef names.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_2">www.pourvidalatinflavor.com</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_2">657–208–3889</string>

    <string name="food_place_name_3">Garlic and Chives</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_3">9892 Westminster Blvd #311, Garden Grove, CA 92844</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_3">Garlic and Chives is a certifiable Little Saigon hit.
        The strip mall space continues to draw legions of fans, eager to try the varied
        Vietnamese fare, from seafood specialities to soups to noodles on down.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_3">www.garlicandchives.com</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_3">714–591–5196</string>

    <string name="food_place_name_4">Burritos La Palma - Santa Ana</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_4">410 N Bristol St, Santa Ana, CA 92703</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_4">Burritos La Palma is a Mexican food institution
        around the Southland, known for palm-sized wrapped tacos filled with slowly-braised meats.
        Simplicity rules here, with diners lining up to catch three, four, or more of the hefty
        mini-burritos at a clip for one seriously filling lunch or early dinner.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_4">burritoslapalma.net</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_4">657–266–0575</string>

    <string name="food_place_name_5">Taco Maria</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_5">3313 Hyland Ave, Costa Mesa, CA, 92626</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_5">Carlos Salgado rightfully continues to earn accolades
        for his upscale modern Mexican restaurant at the OC Mix Mart, which — besides being
        delicious — actively seeks out pre-Hispanic ingredients and heirloom products to work
        with. Taco Maria is, in many ways, still helping to change the way Orange County
        thinks about Mexican food.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_5">tacomaria.com</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_5">714–538–8444</string>

    <string name="food_place_name_6">Vaca</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_6">695 Town Center Dr Suit 160, Costa Mesa, CA 92626</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_6">Vaca remains a dining destination for Orange County,
        thanks to chef Amar Santana\'s stint on Top Chef. The Spanish-inflected Costa Mesa
        restaurant hits on all cylinders, from meat to seafood to fresh produce to one of the
        best wine lists in the county.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_6">www.vacarestaurant.com</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_6">714–463–6060</string>

    <string name="food_place_name_7">Mesa</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_7">725 Baker St, Costa Mesa, CA 92626</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_7">Costa Mesa dinner and lounge option Mesa is a special
        kind of place, with its inviting interior and wide array of shareable items.
        Everything is comforting and approachable but done with love, including the craft
        beer and boutique wine list that attracts a weekend crowd.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_7">mesacostamesa.com</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_7">714–557–6700</string>

    <string name="food_place_name_8">Blackmarket Bakery</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_8">2937 Bristol St Ste D100A, Costa Mesa, CA 92626</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_8">One of Orange County\'s finest bake shops, this
        Costa Mesa pastry institution now serves Santa Ana and San Diego as well. Breakfast,
        brunch, lunch, and dessert are all on the table here.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_8">blackmarketbakery.com</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_8">714–662–3095</string>

    <string name="food_place_name_9">Oo Toro Sushi</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_9">2222 Michelson Dr, Irvine, CA 92612</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_9">Upscale Oo Toro Sushi is a hit for the spendy
        faction of Irvine, working a menu of top notch fish and decadent add-ons like
        Wagyu beef from a clean, slick space off Michelson Drive.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_9">ootorosushi.com</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_9">949–222–0688</string>

    <string name="food_place_name_10">Bluegold &amp; LSXO</string>
    <string name="food_place_address_10">21010 Pacific Coast Hwy, Huntington Beach, CA 92648</string>
    <string name="food_place_description_10">Blackhouse Hospitality has pushed into Orange County
        in a big way with LSXO, the glitzy newcomer to the large Pacific City project in
        Huntington Beach. Hidden away inside sister restaurant Bluegold, LSXO is a 28-seat
        high end option working a decidedly clever Southeast Asian menu.</string>
    <string name="food_place_website_10">dinebluegold.com/lsxo</string>
    <string name="food_place_phone_10">714–374–0083</string>

    <!-- Theme Parks info -->
    <string name="theme_park_name_1">Disney California Adventure Park</string>
    <string name="theme_park_address_1">1313 Disneyland Drive, Anaheim, CA 92803–3232</string>
    <string name="theme_park_description_1">Experience the thrill of the an old wooden
        rollercoaster, but with modern twists, turns and technology, at "California Screamin."
        Or enjoy a live performance by your favorite characters at Disney\'s newest theme park,
        featuring a slew of exciting rides and family entertainment.</string>
    <string name="theme_park_website_1">disneyland.disney.go.com/destinations/disney-california-adventure/?CMP=OKC-dlr_TA_173</string>
    <string name="theme_park_phone_1">714–781–4565</string>

    <string name="theme_park_name_2">Knott\'s Berry Farm</string>
    <string name="theme_park_address_2">8039 Beach Blvd, Buena Park, CA 90620–3225</string>
    <string name="theme_park_description_2">Once a working berry farm, this popular theme park
        is now home to GhostRider, the world\'s best wooden roller coaster; Supreme Scream,
        a ride where participants are hoisted up 30-stories and dropped down in three seconds;
        the Xcelerator, rated the world\'s best launch coaster and Camp Snoopy, home to
        the beloved Peanuts gang.</string>
    <string name="theme_park_website_2">www.knotts.com</string>
    <string name="theme_park_phone_2">714–220–5200</string>

    <string name="theme_park_name_3">Adventure City</string>
    <string name="theme_park_address_3">1238 S Beach Blvd, Anaheim, CA 92804</string>
    <string name="theme_park_description_3">Adventure City is the little theme park that\'s
        big on family fun! Admission for a family of four is less than a ticket to a big park
        so you can enjoy all of our 17 rides, shows and attractions for one affordable price!
        Experience thrills on one of our two roller coasters including our newest coaster,
        Rewind Racers. North America\'s first forward and reversing family shuttle coaster.
        Take a ride on the Adventure City Express Train for a scenic trip around the park or
        get a little loony on the crazy bus. Meet some new animal friends in our petting farm.
        Enjoy fun, interactive children\'s shows and so much more! Adventure City, Orange
        County\'s premier destination for affordable family fun!</string>
    <string name="theme_park_website_3">www.adventurecity.com</string>
    <string name="theme_park_phone_3">714–236–9300</string>

    <string name="theme_park_name_4">Boomers! Irvine</string>
    <string name="theme_park_address_4">3405 Michelson Dr, Irvine, CA 92612–1605</string>
    <string name="theme_park_description_4">When it comes to fun, Boomers! Is a blast! Whether
        you\'re celebrating a birthday, having a party, doing corporate parties,
        events and team building, or spending quality time with family and friends,
        Boomers makes everything easier and hassle free. With attractions like Batting Cages,
        Thrill Rides, Miniature Golf, Go Karts, Bumper Boats, Laser Tag, Rock Wall, Arcade,
        King Arthur\'s Carnival and Lil\' Thunder Road, Boomers is the perfect place
        for fun! It\'s a super-sized water play area that\'s five levels high with
        slippery slides, wet tunnels, spray loops and a huge splash bucket. Make the fun
        happen with spray cannons and the interactive aqua dome. This new water play park
        includes over 1000 feet of water slides. And if you just want to watch the action,
        kick back in a comfy lounge chair.</string>
    <string name="theme_park_website_4">www.boomersparks.com/site/irvine</string>
    <string name="theme_park_phone_4">949–559–8336</string>

    <string name="theme_park_name_5">Universal Studios Hollywood</string>
    <string name="theme_park_address_5">100 Universal City Plaza, Universal City, CA 91608</string>
    <string name="theme_park_description_5">Find a full day of action-packed entertainment
        all in one place: thrilling Theme Park rides and shows, a real working movie studio,
        and Los Angeles\' best shops, restaurants and cinemas at CityWalk. Universal
        Studios Hollywood is a unique experience that\'s fun for the whole family.</string>
    <string name="theme_park_website_5">www.universalstudioshollywood.com</string>
    <string name="theme_park_phone_5">800–864–8377</string>

    <string name="theme_park_name_6">Great Wolf Lodge Southern California</string>
    <string name="theme_park_address_6">12681 Harbor Blvd, Garden Grove CA 92840</string>
    <string name="theme_park_description_6">The Great Wolf Lodge Southern California is
        California\'s first indoor waterpark. This 603 room hotel incorporates a
        121,000 square foot indoor water park, making it the largest Great Wolf Lodge
        resort in existence. The resort gives visitors the option to stay in a themed suite,
        allowing you to huddle in the wolf\'s den or cozy up in a cabin themed suite. This
        hotel is perfect for a variety of family friendly activities. Families can be a part of
        a lunch time line up of activities and play at the indoor waterpark. Entrance to the
        indoor water park is included in hotel rates and is exclusively offered to hotel guest.
        The waterpark has over 15 attractions and activities that are the epitome of aquatic fun.</string>
    <string name="theme_park_website_6">www.greatwolf.com/southern-california</string>
    <string name="theme_park_phone_6">714–530–9653</string>

    <string name="theme_park_name_7">Orange County Great Park</string>
    <string name="theme_park_address_7">Sand Canyon &amp; Marine Drive, Irvine CA 92869</string>
    <string name="theme_park_description_7">Hundreds of thousands of visitors from all over Southern
        California enjoy the Orange County Great Park\'s current array of recreational
        and educational opportunities, including views from the iconic Great Park Balloon
        that rises 400 feet in the air and provides a panoramic view of Orange County.
        Other Great Park features include the Carousel, Farm + Food Lab, Kids Rock Playground,
        Walkable Historical Timeline, Palm Court Arts Complex, North Lawn recreation area and
        historic Hangar 244. The Great Park also hosts a variety of special events that provide
        unique experiences for the entire family, including the Growing the Park Anniversary
        Celebration, annual Pumpkin Harvest, Great Night! Family New Year\'s Eve,
        Flights &amp; Sounds Summer Festival and the weekly Great Park Farmers Market.</string>
    <string name="theme_park_website_7">www.ocgp.org</string>
    <string name="theme_park_phone_7">949–724–6574</string>

    <!-- Wildlife areas info -->
    <string name="wildlife_area_name_1">Sherman Library &amp; Gardens</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_1">2647 Pacific Coast Hwy, Newport Beach, CA 92625</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_1">Horticultural retreat that features a museum of
        living plants, walking paths, bubbling tile fountains and a library devoted to
        the study of the Pacific Southwest.</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_1">www.slgardens.org</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_1">949–673–2261</string>

    <string name="wildlife_area_name_2">San Joaquin Wildlife Santuary</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_2">5 Riparian View, Irvine CA 92612, Irvine, CA 92612</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_2">Go before sunset and watch all the birds flying
        in from the surrounding area. There are an unbelievable number of birds in this man-made
        wetlands on the grounds of a water reclamation plant. The paths are flat (but dirt)
        and easy to walk around the different pools. There are several parking lots along
        Riparian Way and at sunset you will see photographers taking photos. There are surprises
        at every turn. Birds fill the sky, Pelicans on a island, egrets, birds of prey, ducks,
        American coots, Red Eye Western Grebe, lots of wading birds including black neck
        stilts and white face ibis. You will see an amazing variety of birds and very few
        people on a weekday around sunset. It\'s a hidden gem!</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_2">www.pourvidalatinflavor.com</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_2">949–261–7963</string>

    <string name="wildlife_area_name_3">Whiting Ranch Wilderness Park</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_3">26701 Portola Parkway, Foothill Ranch, CA 92610</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_3">Whiting Ranch Wilderness Park encompasses
        approximately 2,500 acres of riparian and oak woodland canyons, rolling grassland
        hills and steep slopes of coastal sage scrub and chaparral. The park is highlighted
        by scenic rock formations, including the beautiful Red Rock Canyon. There are three
        intermittent streams: Borrego, Serrano and Aliso Creek meandering through the park,
        each hosting an abundance of wildlife. Remnants of the former cattle ranching
        days can be seen throughout the park.</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_3">www.ocparks.com/parks/whiting</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_3">949–923–2245 </string>

    <string name="wildlife_area_name_4">Rancho Las Lomas Wildlife Foundation</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_4">19191 Lawrence Cyn, Silverado, CA 92676–9731</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_4">Rancho Las Lomas Wildlife Foundation is an open-air
        museum that lives, breathes, squawks and growls. Our dedication is to educate and inspire
        the community about the wonders of the natural world, while helping all realize every
        creature of this planet deserves the right to live with compassion and respect.</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_4">ranchowildlife.org</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_4">949–589–7900</string>

    <string name="wildlife_area_name_5">Bolsa Chica Ecological Reserve</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_5">Entrance, Huntington Beach, CA 92647</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_5">Bolsa Chica is a small area just North of
        Huntington Beach Dog Back on Pacific Coast Highway that provides visitors an
        opportunity to observe, photograph and relax in a little oasis on the way to
        Seal Beach in California. There is a small parking lot connecting to Pacific Coast Highway.
        After exiting your vehicle, you notice a walkway to the North that is paved.
        Directly ahead is a wooden sturdy bridge leading to the opposite bank.
        Water in the pool has direct access to the Pacific Ocean. As the tide comes in,
        the water level increases. Ocean birds congregate in the protected area. There
        is no hunting or fishing within this area. There you will find an abundance of
        photographers. The scope and variety of birds will keep you excited about what
        you will see next. There are also sea animals that may enter and leave at will.
        It is a nice place to unplug from the civilization for a while.</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_5">bolsachica.org</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_5">714–846–1114</string>

    <string name="wildlife_area_name_6">Thomas F. Riley Wilderness Park</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_6">30952 Oso Pkwy, Trabuco Canyon, CA 92679–5377</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_6">Riley park is a very nice park just to take a
        break and unwind. There are a few trails that do have an encline that will get
        your legs and heart working. Once on top the view is very much worth it!
        The park is well maintained with an Interpretive Center that holds much
        of the parks history.</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_6">ocparks.com/parks/thomas</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_6">714–771–6731</string>

    <string name="wildlife_area_name_7">Seal Beach National Wildlife Refuge</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_7">800 Seal Beach Blvd, Seal Beach, CA 90740–5607</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_7">The National Wildlife Refuge in Seal Beach offers
        opportunities to see what is being done to protect our endangered species and wetlands,
        conservation efforts to protect native habitat, and raise awareness about the human impact
        on our environment. A tour of the Refuge is offered on the last Saturday of the month
        (as noted in the Seal Beach Sun). The tour is interesting and eye-opening and well worth the
        time. It is especially good for school groups, clubs, scouts, and community members who
        want to learn about wildlife and environmental issues. When you travel on PCH, a section
        of the highway between Seal Beach and Sunset Beach has been adopted by the Friends
        of the Refuge—another indication of the concern the Refuge volunteers have for our
        local environment. Participate and support the efforts of the
        Seal Beach National Wildlife Refuge!</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_7">cnic.navy.mil</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_7">562–598–1024</string>

    <string name="wildlife_area_name_8">Pacific Marine Mammal Center</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_8">20612 Laguna Canyon Rd, Laguna Beach, CA 92651</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_8">The Pacific Marine Mammal Center rescues,
        rehabilitates and releases marine mammals and inspires ocean stewardship through research,
        education and collaboration. We are open to the public for visitors every day from
        10am - 4pm. We are closed on Thanksgiving, Christmas Eve, Christmas Day,
        and New Years Day. There is no charge for visiting us, but donations are appreciated!</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_8">www.pacificmmc.org</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_8">949–494–3050</string>

    <string name="wildlife_area_name_9">Peters Canyon Regional Park</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_9">8548 Canyon View Ave, Orange, CA 92869–5883</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_9">Peters Canyon Regional Park is a beautiful hiking
        park. The trails are well developed with use. It is rare to find yourself alone on
        the trails - they are much used and much loved. The hikes offer a variety of levels
        so read the maps in the parking lot. The lake has been dry for a few years, but
        when the lake is full, your hike will feel like you have found Heaven. The
        parking lot is small. You can park in the neighborhoods around Peter\'s Canyon Park,
        but be respectful of homeowners and their property. Pack a snack and hike to the highest
        point in the park. You\'ll be thrilled with the find of a park bench and one
        BEAUTIFUL view of OC. This is a hiking park you don\'t want to miss.</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_9">ocparks.com/parks/peters</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_9">714–973–6611</string>

    <string name="wildlife_area_name_10">Upper Newport Bay Nature Preserve</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_address_10">2301 University Dr, Newport Beach, CA 92660–3310</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_description_10">It\'s one of the few natural resources
        left in the area. Enjoy the local flora and fauna and some nature in a place that has
        been heavily developed. Local school kids know this well as the best place to get
        your bug collection for the school science project.</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_website_10">www.ocparks.com/uppernewportbay</string>
    <string name="wildlife_area_phone_10">949–923–2290</string>

</resources>
